Guide to the Gerrit Lansing Papers YCAL MSS 469
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- August 2019 acquisition, 1814–2018; Bulk, 1950–2018; 8; 53.85 Linear Feet (66 boxes)
  - Computer media, 2018 (Box 82)
    Box 82 (computer media): Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
- January 2020 acquisition, 1939–2003; 9; 0.13 Linear Feet (1 box)
  This series contains printed and manuscript sheet music, notes, and "In the Company of Love," a song cycle for soprano and piano, with poems by Gerrit Lansing and music by Bruce Wolosoff. Materials are dated from 1939 to 2003.
  Gift of Gary Gorczyca, 2020.
  - Assorted papers, 1993-2003, undated (Box 83)
    Includes notes by Lansing, a poetry broadside by Ange Mlinko, and writings and a letter in an unknown hand.
  - "Claremont Concerto" by Gene Carl, inscribed to Lansing, 1999 (Box 83)
  - "Drei Klavierstücke" by Arnold Schoenberg, annotated by Lansing, undated (Box 83)
  - "Estampes" by Claude Debussy, inscribed to Lansing from "Joe", 1953 (Box 83)
  - "In the Company of Love," poems by Gerrit Lansing, music by Bruce Wolosoff, undated (Box 83)
  - "Lenore" by Franz Liszt, annotated in unknown hand, undated (Box 83)
  - Music notebooks [belonging to Lansing?], undated (Box 83)
  - Printed music, undated (Box 83)
  - "Sonatina for Piano" by Donald Fuller, 1939–1940 (Box 83)